&gt；&gt；steve kinney：有点进入我们的下一个主题，这是一个问题，
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Kinda move into our
next topic, which is the issue of,
我们现在知道了很多关于快速制作东西的方法。
we now know a lot about making stuff fast.
我们知道如何诊断慢的东西。
We know how to diagnose
things that are slow.
我们知道如何调整，但是
We know how to adjust things, but
我们需要做的就是将这些东西放到浏览器上，以便处理这些东西。
what we need to do is get those things
to the browser in order to handle those.
这本身就是一门很好的艺术。
And that is a fine art in and of itself.
首先我们要讨论的是延迟和带宽，对吗？
First that we're gonna talk about
is Latency and Bandwidth, right?
这是影响你获得网页速度的两个重要因素。
These are two important factors into
the speed in which you get a webpage.
我想第三个因素是你发送了多少网页，对吗？
I guess the third factor is how
much webpage you're sending, right?
我们看到那个酒吧一直在上升。
We saw that bar keep going up and
up and up and up.
因此这些变得越来越重要。
So these become increasingly important.
我们考虑了很多关于带宽的问题。
We think a lot about bandwidth.
很多时候，我们不会考虑太多的延迟。
A lot of times,
we don't think a lot about latency.
所以我们要探索一下他们两个。
So we're gonna kinda explore both of them.
但首先，我很喜欢亚历克斯·罗素的这句话。
But first, there's this quote from
Alex Russell that I really like.
当我们在Web应用程序、网络CPU和
That effectively when we're working
on web applications, network CPUs and
磁盘都讨厌你。
disks all hate you.
在客户端，你以你不容易看到的方式为你发送的东西付费。
On the client, you pay for what you
send in ways you can't easily see.
我们通过解析看到了这一点，对吗？
We saw that with parsing, right?
我们看到JPEG和JavaScript文件是不一样的，对吧？
We saw the JPEG and a JavaScript
file aren't created equal, right?
还有一大堆其他因素可以发挥作用。
There's a whole bunch of other
factors to play into this.
所以对于那些不知道的人来说，互联网是一系列的管道。
So for those of you who don't know,
that the Internet is a series of tubes.
基本上，猫的迷因开始于某一点。
That basically,
a cat meme starts at one point.
它通过管道，并最终在你的浏览器中成为一个猫的迷因。
It goes through the tubes, and
ends up in your browser to be a cat meme.
在你的浏览器上引起了无法估量的喜悦，对吗？
On your browser causing
an immeasurable amount of joy, right?
所以管子有两个维度。
And so that tube has two dimensions.
带宽是指管子的宽度。
Bandwidth is how wide the tube is.
在给定的时刻，你可以通过管子装多少东西。
How much stuff can you fit through
the tube at a given moment.
很明显，
And obviously,
你的管子越宽，你可以穿过管子的猫迷因就越多。
the wider your tube, the more cat memes
that you can shove through the tube.
这很直观，对吧？
This makes intuitive sense, right?
更大的管子，更多的猫，完成了。
Bigger tube, more cats, done.
另一个问题是你的管子有多长，对吧？
The other problem is how
long is your tube, right?
如果管子必须绕过半个地球，
If the tube has to go
halfway around the world,
那些猫要花更长的时间才能找到你。
those cats are gonna take
longer to get to you.
当然，你可以把一大堆猫塞进管子里，然后推着它们走。
Sure, you can shove a whole lot of
cats in that tube and push them along.
但是猫的物理定律规定将会有一定量的
But the laws of cat physics dictate that
there is going to be a certain amount of
是时候让第一批猫找到你了。
time for
that first payload of cats to get to you.
所以这两者都是我们需要考虑的因素。
So this are both like factors that
we kinda need to think about.
中间有一段非常棒的视频。
And there's this really
great video on center.
歌，它就像野生的它和看到的事情。
Song it's like wild it and see matters.
而我真正喜欢的部分是这种视觉效果。
And the part that I really
like it's this visual.
他们在这里做了一大堆指标。
They did a bunch of metrics here.
这就是全部，就像你可以看到西德尼是最好的，这是基于我的一个。
This is all, like you can see that Sidney
is the best, this is based out of my one.
所以这是一个重要的测试笔记。
So that's an important testing note.
当我看着它的时候，哇，西德尼有一些快速的互联网。
And when I looking at it, wow,
Sidney's got some fast Internet.
他们有非常快的互联网到墨尔本[笑]为
They've got very fast Internet
to Melbourne [LAUGH] as
与圣何塞和伦敦相比。
compared to San Jose and London.
但是，您可以看到，随着文件大小的增加，
But, you can see that
as file size increases,
下载时间并不是以线性的方式上升。
download time isn't in
a linear fashion going up.
不仅仅是，是的，文件大小变大了。
It's not just, yeah,
the file size gets bigger.
它正在采取这些巨大的步骤，而它需要的时间越来越长。
It's taking these massive steps
where it's taking longer and longer.
对于每个LIKE，随着文件大小的增长，这些LIKE会跳跃。
For like every like,
as the file size grows, these like jumps.
这看起来很奇怪，但实际上就像TCP的报价取消报价功能，对吧？
Which seems strange, but is actually like
a quote unquote feature of TCP, right?
那么TCP，传输控制协议，对吗？
So TCP,
the transmission control protocol, right?
它的工作，不一定是让你的东西快。
Its job, it's not necessarily
to get you stuff fast.
你会想，哇，为什么互联网上的一个主要管道生物不在
You'd be like, wow, why is one of the
major pipe beings of the Internet not in
负责快速给我拿东西？
charge of getting me stuff fast?
因为它主要关注的是可靠地得到你的东西，对吗？
Cuz it's primarily focused with
getting you stuff reliably, right?
让你所有的比特都按正确的顺序排列，并且
Getting you all of the bits
in the right order, and
这样做会牺牲速度。
it will sacrifice speed to do that.
我之前说过
I said earlier,
基本上大多数性能都是某种权衡，对吧？
that basically most performance things
are some kind of trade off, right?
与图层一样，您正在用一定数量的内存复杂性来交换
Like layers, you're trading a certain
amount of memory complexity for
更快的油漆时间，对吧？
faster paint times, right?
所有这些，在某些情况下，比如你的超酷JavaScript编译和
All of these things, in some cases like,
your super cool JavaScript compiling and
解析hack可能会影响可读性，对吧？
parsing hack is maybe
affecting readability, right?
这就是你需要考虑的事情。
That's the thing you need to think of.
那里也总是有人的因素。
There's always that
human element there too.
TCP的工作方式是，
The way TCP works is,
它会继续与服务器进行检查，以确保一切正常。
it continues checking with the server
to make sure everything's working well.
我们正在按正确的顺序接收数据包。
We're getting the packets
in the correct order.
他们在管子里没有被腐蚀。
They're not getting corrupted in the tube.
客户端在接收到每个包时已经确认。
That the client has acknowledged
with receipt of each package.
不可靠的连接处理得很好。
Unreliable connections are handled well.
我们没有让网络超载，对吧。
We're not overloading the network, right.
所以它就像，非常小心地确保一切都进行得令人难以置信的顺利。
And so it's like, very careful to make
sure everything's going incredibly well.
这样我们就可以确保不会有丢失或损坏的文件。
That way we make sure we don't have
files that go missing, or get corrupted.
因为如果你收到一个损坏的猫gif。
Because if you receive
a corrupted cat gif.
在这一点上，在互联网上到底有什么意义呢？
What is even the point of being
on the Internet at that point?
我只是关上我的笔记本电脑出去或者别的什么，也许读一本书？
I'm just gonna close my laptop and go
outside or something, maybe read a book?
就像，谁想这么做？
Like, who wants to do that?
因此TCP从发送少量数据开始。
So TCP starts by sending
a small amount of data.
如果进展顺利，它就会开始发送更多，而且
If that goes well,
it starts sending more, and
更多，因为它发现事情是成功的。
more, as it finds out things
are being successful.
这就是你看到那些大跳跃的原因。
And that's why you saw those big jumps.
所以它一开始就没有发送尽可能多的数据。
So it starts out by not sending
as much data as it could.
就像，让我给你发一小包数据。
Like, let me send you a tiny
little packet of data.
你拿到了吗？
Did you get it?
酷毙了。
Cool.
在我知道你已经得到了很多次之后。
After I know you've gotten
it a bunch of times.
它几乎就像优化编译器。
It's almost like the optimizing compiler.
事情进展顺利吗？
Things are going well?
我会开始高速运转的，对吧？
I'll start kicking things into high gear,
right?
但是同样，相反的也是正确的。
But the also, the opposite is true.
这就是为什么在慢速连接时事情会感觉如此糟糕的原因。
This is why things feel so
much worse on a slow connection.
因为数据包丢失了。
Because packets get lost.
他们会堕落。
They get corrupted.
因此TCP从小元数据开始。
So TCP starts by saying small metadata.
您的连接已经不可靠。
Your connection is already unreliable.
已经很慢了。
So already slow.
所以给你发了一小包数据。
So sends you a small packet of data.
其中一些会被破坏。
Some of those get corrupted.
再发一次。
Sends them again.
它不像一个互联网连接，
It's not like an Internet
connection that's like,
可靠性的一半就是速度的一半。
half as reliable is half as fast.
指数慢，因为TCP就像，我不信任你。
Exponentially slower because TCP is like,
I don’t trust you.
我要把猫放到YouTube上。
I am putting cats on YouTube.
YouTube在泄露，对吧
YouTube is leaking, right.
你仍然有YouTube，然后你得到了你应得的猫。
You still have YouTube, and
then you get the cats you deserve.
CCP在不可靠的连接下会变得更糟，比如戏剧性的方式。
CCP will be worse under unreliable
connections like dramatic ways.
所以，是的，我们都知道这一点。
So yeah, and we all know this.
不可靠的互联网比没有互联网更糟糕，酷。
Unreliable internet is worse
than no internet, cool.
所以，这只是一个有趣的事实，当我们得到文件大小在一点点。
So just a fun fact,
when we get to file sizes in a little bit.
TCP的初始窗口大小是14千字节。
Is that the initial window
size of TCP is 14 kilobytes.
这意味着如果你能获得低于14千字节的任何资产。
Which means if you can get
whatever asset under 14 kilobytes.
您可以一次发送。
You can send it in one go.
如果是28，我们就得开始握手了。
If it's 28,
then we got to start doing the handshake.
你拿到前14个了吗？
Did you get the first 14?
酷毙了。
Cool.
我会在接下来的14天寄给你。
I'll send you the next 14.
等等，对吧？
So on and so forth, right?
这很有趣，因为像我们的JavaScript应用程序正在增长，对吗？
And it's interesting because like our
JavaScript apps are growing, right?
就像这看起来像14千字节[笑]那是不会发生的，对吧。
Like this seems like 14 kilobytes
[LAUGH] that's not gonna happen, right.
也许吧。我们有一些小把戏在我们的袖子里。
Maybe.
We have some tricks up our sleeves.
但是，是的，如果我们能把它放进去，就会好很多，对吧？
But yeah, if we could get that in
there it would be way better, right?
这就是构建网络的管道的本质。
This is just the nature of the plumbing
that the web is built upon.
所以，让我们实际看看这一点。
So let's actually kind
of see that in action.
我们要去
We're gonna go to
http://www.cloudping.info/&GT；&GT；史蒂夫·金尼：以及
http://www.cloudping.info/
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: And
有很多不同的工具可以做到这一点，而且
there's a bunch of different
tools that do this, and
你应该看看他们所有的，因为他们都很酷。
you should check out all of
them because they're very cool.
基本上是从我们现在明尼苏达州的地方。
Basically from where we are right now,
in Minnesota.
我们可以袭击很多亚马逊地区。
We can hit a bunch of Amazon regions.
好的，从弗吉尼亚州的美国东部到俄亥俄州，一直到
All right, everywhere from US-East in
Virginia, to Ohio, all the way out to
加州，一路延伸到南美，印度，等等。
California, all the way out to
South America, India, so on and so forth.
所以我们会继续和ping。
So we'll go ahead and ping.
&gt；&gt；steve kinney：你可以看到物理的简单定律，
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: You can see
the simple laws of physics,
电子只能以这么快的速度通过导线，
that electrons can only
go through wires so fast,
就像光速是一种东西一样，是的，互联网受到物理学的约束。
like the speed of light is a thing, and
yes, the Internet is bound by physics.
大多数时候看起来不像，但确实是。
Doesn't seem like it most of the time,
but it definitely is.
所以我们离得越远，我们的时间就越慢，
And so the further away we get,
the slower our times are,
我认为这很吸引人，对吧？
which I think is fascinating, right?
我们可以谈谈如何解决这个问题。
And we can talk a little bit
about how to solve this problem.
实际上，它既令人难以置信地复杂，又天真地简单。
It's actually both incredibly
complicated and naively simply.
它做起来难以置信的复杂和天真的简单对我们来说，
It's incredibly complicated to do and
naively simple for us to do,
因为我们让别人来做这项工作。
because we let somebody else do the work.
这也是获得表演的方式。
That is also the way to get performances.
第三条规则，如果有工作要做，
Third rule, if work has to be done,
其他人可以做这项工作可能也是有用的。
can someone else do this work
is probably useful as well.
&gt；&gt；steve kinney：所以，你知道，我在丹佛工作。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: So, you know like,
I work it's in Denver.
我肯定我们会把我们的资产放在丹佛，对吧？
I'm sure we place our assets in Denver,
right?
我们的客户大多在哪里？
Where are most of our customers?
他们在美国吗？
Are they in the United States?
我不知道，可能吧。
I don't know, like probably.
如果我们想让人们快速获得我们的资产，我们应该把它们放在哪里？
Where do we put our assets if
we want people to get them fast?
知道如果我们把他们放在丹佛
Knowing that if we put them in Denver,
想要在北京买到它们的人将很难得到它。
people trying to get them in Beijing
are going to have a hard time getting it.
在墨尔本，情况会更糟，如此等等。
In Melbourne it's gonna be even worse,
so on and so forth.
那我们把它们放在哪里？
So where do we put them?
答案无处不在。
The answer is everywhere.
你觉得这不能令人满意。
You're like that's unsatisfying.
通常答案是使用CDN。
And usually the answer is using a CDN.
这是云的前沿，稍后我将讨论一些简单的方法来做到这一点。
This is cloud front and later on I'm gonna
talk about some easy ways to do this.
好像两者都有，
Like there's both,
这是其中一件事情，它甚至不是关于它有多难。
it's one of those things where it's
not even on how difficult it is.
但基本上，云前沿是有很多地方可以托管DSS。
But basically cloud front is that there
are a bunch of places to host DSS.
世界上有一大堆我们称之为边缘节点的东西。
There's a bunch of like we call
edge nodes all around the world.
每个客户端与其最近的边缘节点交谈，
Each client talks to
their closest edge node,
理想情况下可以更快地拿到东西。
which ideally can get them stuff faster.
所以你只是到处散布，到处缓存。
So you just spread it around everywhere,
caching it all over the place.
我会稍微谈一下，但我现在会破坏一些惊喜。
I'll talk about this a little, but
I'll ruin some of the surprise now.
如果是，嘿，我一直在研究这件事就像我自己的项目一样，而且
If it's, hey, I've been working on this
thing like my own side project, and
这是一个小应用程序。
it's a small application.
有很多服务可以很容易地为你做到这一点。
There are a bunch of services that
will do this for you really easily.
如果你是一个大公司，其实亚马逊会让它不难，对吧？
If you are a large company, actually,
Amazon will make it not hard, right?
几个月后我要去上一堂AWS课程。
I'm gonna do a AWS class in a few months.
在那里我们将讨论如何设置所有这些。
Where we'll talk about
how to set that all up.
但这有点难，如果你想建立自己的CDN，
But it's a slightly hard,
if you wanna build your own CDN,
如果你想成为亚马逊或CloudFlare，那就是，
if you want to be Amazon or
CloudFlare, well that would be,
你需要喜欢在世界各地设置东西。
you need to like do the setting up
of things all around the world.
但是对于你们这些在房间里的人来说，那里有一张世界的图片。
But for those of you in the room,
there's a picture of the world there.
当我看着屏幕时，那看起来就像点一样。
That just looks like dots
as I look at the screen.
但是想象一下世界的灰色剪影。
But imagine a grey
silhouette of the world.
那边那个大集群是美国。
That big cluster over there
is the United States.
那边是中国，下面是澳大利亚。
Over there we have China,
and down below Australia.
所以对我们大多数人来说我们要么
So yeah, for most of us we're either,
它在利用别人的内容分发网络，对吗？
it's leveraging somebody else's
content distribution network, right?
把它放在那些地方。
And putting it in those places.
但是，你的民事行为确实需要这样做，对吧？
But, the civil act of you
do need to do it, right?
有些服务会免费为你做这件事。
Some services will do it for you for free.
会自动，但不是每个人都能开箱。
Will automatically, but
not everyone out of the box.
如果您只有一台服务器，并且他们正在为您提供正常的后端服务，
And if you just have a server and they're
serving your normal back-end services and
你只是把文件放在那里，你可能没有CDN。
you just put the files there,
you likely don't have a CDN.